Finding Aid for Men's Glee Club (University of Michigan) records 1886-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings 1952-1987
  - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 127th Fall Concert November 15, 1986, 2 reels (Box 18)
  - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 127th Annual Spring Concert, 11 April 1987, 2 reels (Box 18)
  - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 128th Fall Concert with the University of Notre Dame Glee Club November 21, 1987, 4 reels (Box 18)
  - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club and Unlabeled Tapes Undated, 4 reels (Box 18)
- China Concert Tour 2012
  In May 2012, the Men's Glee Club embarked on a two-week concert tour of the People's Republic of China that included visits to Beijing (May 3 to May 5), Xi'an (May 5 to May 8), Chongquing (May 8 to May 11), Wuhan (May 11 to May 13), and Shanghai (May 13 to May 16). The resulting China Concert Tour series is organized around the itinerary and includes digital images shot by club members in various locales, audio and video footage of performances at major stops and video of various excursions in host cities. The series is organized according to the Glee Club's itinerary; through: Of note is the concert performance given at Ba Shu Secondary School (Chongqing)and visits to notable sites such as the Great Wall, Tiananmen Square, the Forbidden City, and Olympic Park (Beijing).
  - Beijing May 3-5, 2012
    - Arrival May 3, 2012
      - Digital images of Glee Clubs Arrival in Beijing
    - Forbidden City May 4, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to the Forbidden City
    - Tiananmen Square May 4, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to Tiananmen Square
    - Tsinghua University Meng Minwei Concert Hall May 4, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at Tsinghua University
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at Tsinghua University
      - Video recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at Tsinghua University
    - Great Wall of China May 5, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club at the Great Wall of China
      - Video recording of the Men's Glee Club singing at the Great Wall of China
    - Jade Factory May 5, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to a jade factory in Beijing
    - Olympic Park May 5, 2012
      - (Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to the site of the 2008 Summer Olympic Games.
    - Tea Ceremony May 5, 2012
      - (Digital images of the Men's Glee Club participating in a tea ceremony
  - Xi'an (May 5 to May 8, 2012)
    - Concert Hall May 6, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at Xi'an Concert Hall
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at Xi'an Concert Hall
    - City Wall May 7, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to the Xi'an city walls
    - Terracotta Warriors May 7, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club excursion to see the terracotta warriors of Xi'an.
  - Chongqing (May 8 to May 11, 2012)
    - Er Ling Park May 8, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club tour of Er Ling Park
      - Video recording of the Men's Glee Club tour of Er Ling Park
    - Ba Shu Secondary School May 9, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to Ba Shu Secondary School
      - Video recordings
        - Men's Glee Club's arrival at Ba Shu Secondary School
        - Ba Shu Secondary School staff remarks
        - Student martial arts demonstration
        - Speeches by Men's Glee Club members, 3 digital files
        - Rehearsal by the Men's Glee Club
        - Vocal performance by the Men's Glee Club, 4 digital files
    - Dazu Stone Carving Park May 9, 2012
      - Digital images of Men's Glee Club excursion to Dazu Stone Carving Park, a World Heritage Site
    - Dongwuyuan May 10, 2012
      - (Digital images of the Men's Glee Club's visit to Chongqing Dongquyuan (Zoo
    - Grand Theater May 10, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Chongqing Grand Theater
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Chongqing Grand Theater
      - Video recordings
        - Men's Glee Club tour of the Chongqing Grand Theater
        - Men's Glee Club rehearsal at the Chongqing Grand Theater
  - Wuhan (May 11 to May 13, 2012)
    - Han Kou waterfront on the Yangtze River May 11, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club excursion to the Han Koue waterfront
    - Hubei Provincial Museum May 12, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to the Hubei Provincial Museum
    - Qintai Grand Theater May 12, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Qintai Grand Theater
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Qintai Grand Theater
      - Video recordings
        - Men's Glee Club tour of the Qintai Grand Theater
        - Men's Glee Club rehearsal at the Qintai Grand Theater
  - Shanghai (May 13 to May 16, 2012)
    - Oriental Art Center May 13, 2012
      - Audio recording of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club performance at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center
      - Video recordings
        - Mens' Glee Club rehearsal for concert at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center
        - Mens' Glee Club performance at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center, 6 digital files
        - Post-concert cleanup and mingling at the Shanghai Oriental Art Center
    - Yu Yuan Garden May 14, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to Yu Yuan Garden
- Archived Website
  - Archived Men's Glee Club website, 2011-[ONGOING]